Good morning.
I'm curious about you.
Yeah.
I'd like to wear a comforter, too.
I told you it's a secret.
Oh, wow.
The ocean.
Close your ears to the sound of the ocean.
Do you hear that daboom?
Daboom.
Oh, okay.
You're the first sisters!
First sisters.
That's right.
The sisters before us are no more.
That's sad.
Oh, no.
It's going to be delicious!
Good morning.
Good morning. - Good morning. - Good morning.
What is it, everyone?
Kobi, it's a Sharin Muscat.
Good.
Come on.
When we're done, I'm going to make egg rice now.
I'll have an egg on rice, Aoi.
I'll have an egg, Aoi.I'll have some of Aoi's eggs.
Aoi's eggs.
How do you make these?
These?
You want to use these?
Hurry up.
Can I push it this way?
Open the door.
PKG egg over rice
Under construction
FUK.
What do you say FUK?
Water stick
Bon appétit!
I'm hungry.
I'm scared.
Ah!
Delicious.
Once you try it, you'll be hooked.
For a while.
It's easy, isn't it? I don't have to cook.
No matter how busy the morning is.
That's all you need.
He's out of bed.
Come a little closer.
Okay. Ready.Yes, yes, yes!
Yay!
I'm scared, Chucky.
Is Chucky okay?
Yeah, it's Chucky.
Okay, well, I'm gonna pee my pants.
Yay.
My hair's gonna fall out. Turn it up.
Pee-wee, Chucky!
I'm pee-pee-pee-ing now.
You're polishing.
Yes, I am.
Shakashaka yui.
That's all.
Cute Rina-chan!
We slept together.
We cuddled and slept together.
We slept under the covers together.
I told you it was a secret.
Something like that.
You can make emojis with your feet.
Can you?
I can't get the red one.
The camera...
Oh...
M.
Here's the M for CV.Here is the CV M
Nowhere to be found.
I would like to go for a walk. I love to go for a walk.
Wow! What a not-so-great weather!
Fireworks in the morning! The weather is nice. Let's do fireworks.
Fireworks! Fireworks in the morning!
Oh!
That's the ocean right there.
I should've gone back.
It was cold, but that's not all.
The stars were so beautiful.
The sauna helped me get in shape.
I'm all set.
Oh, my God!
Hey, wake up your ears, there's the sound of the ocean.
Do you hear that daboom?
Daboom.
Oh, my goodness.
I love the sound of the ocean.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, is that a school?
That's amazing.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is amazing.
I'll take a look at that.
Old school.
Seriously? Seriously?
This is definitely the wrong place.
We're gonna sink here.
I can't climb.
I can't climb up here!
It's okay.
The sound of the ocean is so soothing, I can sleep normally.
You're so cool!
Yes, sir.
Shall we go?
What color do you like?
I think we should do two at a time.
I usually don't do all of them.
But we're done.
Let's get it done.
Okay. - Okay.
Give it to me.
It's called "give me.
Here you go.
Let's lighten Lina's load.
Lina's grandmother.
Is the camera okay?
Yay!
She's so cute.
It's got color.
Yeah.
It's true.It's true.
It's over.
It's over, but I'm on fire.
Oh, my God.
He's coming after me.
Oh, my God, that's so emo!
That's so emo.
Oh, my God!
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Emo.
It's so cute.
It's green.
Green!
What's with the wind? It's changing.
Yeah, it's changing.
The wind's changing.
Oh, scary!
Ooh!
I'm scared of the slope.
Green.
All the way to Atda hubby's.
No, you didn't because it's super cool?
I'm adding a picture.
I'm done with the green.
That's so cool.That's really cool.
I love it.
Blue sky
Blue sky.
It looks like a tunnel.
Aoi Oyen
Do you want to sit down for this?
Which one do you hold? This one
Like this.
This way?
You don't know what fireworks are, do you?
Here we go.
Do we have to do them at the same time?
At the same time.
Watch your knees.
The wind's blowing this way again.
You don't think the wind's going to drop?
It might.
Is this coming?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm almost done.
Top's over.
By the time this drops.
That's right.
First sisters.
The first sisters are over.I'm so done with the sisters ahead of me.
It was great back then, wasn't it?
When we were filming... it was a lot of work.
It was hard work.
A lot happened.
I was so shocked that I fell too.
That's right, I fell off too.
I was the first one to fall.
I fell.
That's amazing.
China.
That feels good.
I want to go for a drive with you.
And what was that?
Like some kind of house.
Zelkova House
No, no, no.
Glamping.
We've been talking about glamping all along.
Just in time.
Hubby is...
We just barely made it happen.
It's like...
So there were 21 of us then?
I was there for the Cake House.
Five.
And then we did it.
It felt like it was time.I felt like it was time.
But I felt like you've matured in the way you enjoy sleepovers.
You were calm.
And I ended up sleeping.
Sleeping soundly.
Spending time with everyone like this...
I don't know...
When you graduate...
Days like this...
Almost gone.
It's gone, isn't it?
That was youth, wasn't it?
I really feel like it was my youth.
I'm going to miss them even more after class.
It's still here.
It's more on this side... when you realize it.
It's like a great sense of loss.
You know...
A mood maker.
More like a mood maker... an atmosphere...
Creating an atmosphere
He was always looking around to create an atmosphere.
He was always looking around.
So...
It's fun.
It's going to be fun.
Koba, you know, he's been pulling milk for a long time.I knew that Koba, you know, from the beginning, he kind of pulled milk for me.
He was a really dependable person.
And there were a lot of members who saw his back and thought, "I have to work harder now.
He really saved me.
It was a success.
Rina-chan, too, really, really let me be kind to everyone and cared for me.
I was able to get through any difficult times because you noticed me.
Thank you so much!
Thanks for your hard work
Thanks for your hard work.
Really.
Woo hoo!
Wow, it passes the test.
But it's Nijinbayashi, already!
Two forests.
You and Fu-chan...
Even though it's always been something silly.
You laughed at my trivial words
We laughed a lot.
It was really thanks to Fuu-chan that she kept the atmosphere of the group cheerful.
Really...
Without you, it wouldn't be so bright.
Not cheerful.
I can't be cheerful without you.
So I really appreciate you, guys.
Everybody.
Thank you.
You really saved me.It really saved the day.
Well, you had my support at the end.
What was it, HubLibbers?
To all the HubLibbers and Buddies
Yes, thank you so much for your support over the past 8 years!
From now on, Sakurazaka 46 will no longer be a part of this group...
I have received so many things from the group.
I will carry them in my heart and do my best from now on.
I will continue to do my best from now on.
I will do my best. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Okay, to the rehearsal. It's the last rehearsal.
This anila is the last one, so it's the last rehearsal.
It's not the last rehearsal.
The last rehearsal for the last show.
Let's do our best. Let's go.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye
This was Sakura House.
Thank you for watching.